<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<!--
  If you are running a bot please visit this policy page outlining rules you must respect. http://www.livejournal.com/bots/  
-->
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>The inner workings of Jonathan's Mind</title>
<link>http://legostud.livejournal.com/</link>
-
	<description>
The inner workings of Jonathan's Mind - LiveJournal.com
</description>
<lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2006 03:32:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
<generator>LiveJournal / LiveJournal.com</generator>
-
	<image>
-
	<url>
http://www.livejournal.com/userpic/45075223/10065571
</url>
<title>The inner workings of Jonathan's Mind</title>
<link>http://legostud.livejournal.com/</link>
<width>77</width>
<height>100</height>
</image>
-
	<item>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://legostud.livejournal.com/11991.html</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2006 03:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
<title>Voices in my head</title>
<link>http://legostud.livejournal.com/11991.html</link>
-
	<description>
I'm struggling with what I want and what is right.  I usually side with logic, but this is the first time that the emotional side is really screaming in my head.  I want Linda to move in with me so much.<br /><br />The logical side is grasping to hold on by saying she needs to have a job first for three reasons.  One to help pay some of the added expenses, two as motivation to get over her anxiety and three we both agreed on it.<br /><br />The Emotional side doesn't care, and it's got a lot of good reasons on it's side.  Since I make 40k+ a year, I could probably absorb the extra cost by budgeting my expenses.  What's more important "buying" LEGO or Linda (yes, I actually had to think about this).<br /><br />And what are the extra costs?  Food...gifts...higher rent?  I'm not sure there really are any real extra costs.  Also if my food expense jumps up because I'm eating supper with Linda then my parents food expense will go down.  Good for them and maybe enough that I won't need to pay more for rent.<br /><br />Even if Linda needs to chip in for rent, my parents have accepted labor for rent in the past.  Maybe she can do some work around the house.  Maybe increase the value or make it easier to rent out (another roommate).<br /><br />If it's cash we need, I have so much valuable junk lying around here that I'm sure we could make a couple hundred a month for about a year by selling it on eBay.  This could also be good for Linda to build up feedback on an eBay account so she can do what she really wants to do, sell custom barbies.<br /><br />The logical side of me is having a hard time holding on the "Linda needs a job before she can move in" agreement.
</description>
<comments>http://legostud.livejournal.com/11991.html</comments>
<lj:security>public</lj:security>
</item>
-
	<item>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://legostud.livejournal.com/11655.html</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2006 02:40:43 GMT</pubDate>
<title>ah, finally a little relaxation</title>
<link>http://legostud.livejournal.com/11655.html</link>
-
	<description>
Well sort of.  I'm still trying to finalize Brick Blast so I can be done.  I need to upload photos and get stuff back to Dave and Tom.  Then it will be over and time to start something else.<br /><br />What a Blast this event was.  I spent a lot of time building and planning for it and it all paid off.  I even got sometime to spend with Linda and Cassie outside of the event.  <br /><br />Got to know that I am a much better person when Linda is around.  Friday night she got me to get some sleep.  First she got me to stop setting up because I was a zombie and then got me to stop thinking of what needed to be done so I could fall asleep.  I so Love Linda.<br /><br />I had a lot of fun at the event, but time with Linda was so much better.<br /><br />Notes for the next time I do this event.  I need to push harder to be the secondary or primary coordinator for the event.  There were things that weren't finished and things that were expect of us that were a complete surprise.  Things I'm really good at making sure don't happen.<br /><br />I also need to remember where I have volunteered to be responsible.  I spent most of my focus on the train layout and missed the fact that the Quarry wasn't getting done.  I was the back up and I thought the primary was on the ball.  Apparently he "couldn't make NELUG a priority".  What a crap answer.  If that was so then pass the ball to someone else.  Don't just sit on it so no one can play.  I spent two full days worth of time on that project to see it never run.<br /><br />It's late, I'm now angry again so I'm going to stop here.  Hopefully the venting will help.
</description>
<comments>http://legostud.livejournal.com/11655.html</comments>
<lj:mood>annoyed</lj:mood>
<lj:security>public</lj:security>
</item>
-
	<item>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://legostud.livejournal.com/11514.html</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2006 03:32:49 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://legostud.livejournal.com/11514.html</link>
-
	<description>
<table width="350" align="center" border="0" cellspacing="0" cellpadding="2"><tr><td bgcolor="#DDDDDD" align="center"><font face="Georgia, Times New Roman, Times, serif" style="color:black; font-size: 14pt;"><b>You Are: 60% Dog, 40% Cat</b></font></td></tr><tr><td bgcolor="#EEEEEE"><center><img src="http://images.blogthings.com/areyoumorecatordogquiz/animal-3.jpg" height="100" width="100"></center><font color="#000000"><br />You are a nice blend of cat and dog.<br />You're playful but not too needy. And you're friendly but careful.<br />And while you have your moody moments, you're too happy to stay upset for long.</font></td></tr></table><div align="center"><a href="http://www.blogthings.com/areyoumorecatordogquiz/">Are You More Cat or Dog?</a></div>
</description>
<comments>http://legostud.livejournal.com/11514.html</comments>
<lj:security>public</lj:security>
</item>
-
	<item>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://legostud.livejournal.com/11126.html</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2006 21:06:04 GMT</pubDate>
<title>I'm not perfect</title>
<link>http://legostud.livejournal.com/11126.html</link>
-
	<description>
Discovery of the day.  I really can't build mechanical lego.<br /><br />I tried building a dump truck today for Brick Blast, but it just wouldn't work.  Ended up spending four hours not getting any where.  Very annoying.  However, I know when to admit I can't do something so I called my brother.  He's here now fiddlin away.  He loves this stuff.<br /><br />Once he figures out the technical stuff I can then dress it up to look like a dump truck.  Should be fun.<br /><br />I'm feeling a little guilty, because I want to help him, but I just can't think straight right now.  I was going to continue working on the city road plates so we could at least both be working on lego, but now I just want to take a nap.  Must be the bug I have.<br /><br />Tried something new early this morning to try and feel better, stuck my head under the sheets while I slept.  Nice humid air going into my lungs was a great release.  Finally had some moisture when I coughed or sniffled.  Verse these painful dry coughs.<br /><br />I've been home sick since Thursday.  Took Thursday and Friday off from work to feel better.<br /><br />Thursday was really bad, sore throat and my head was in a cloud.  However, Friday felt much better.  Same sore throat, but my brain was working.  Might have been stress from Brick Blast giving me an adrenaline rush.  Or maybe it was because Linda came over to snuggle.  I love snuggling.<br /><br />I volunteered to help Mike tomorrow work on the mosaic.  Hopefully, I can find something mind numbing enough to do that I won't need to think much.<br /><br />Cough Cough... Hate this damn bug.  It's summer time.  I'm not supposed to be sick during the summer.
</description>
<comments>http://legostud.livejournal.com/11126.html</comments>
<category>sick</category>
<lj:mood>icky</lj:mood>
<lj:security>public</lj:security>
</item>
-
	<item>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://legostud.livejournal.com/10755.html</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2006 15:00:11 GMT</pubDate>
<title>Sick of being home sick</title>
<link>http://legostud.livejournal.com/10755.html</link>
-
	<description>
Came down with some nasty little bug Tuesday.  At first I thought it was just bad air in the house.  We have a forced air system for the AC and heat and sometimes it blows dust around.  Yesterday I realized that it was more than the air in the house, because I felt terrible.  Some sort of sinus thing.  Throat hurts and my head is foggy.<br /><br />I've been realizing that I'm not updating my journal as often as I was hoping to.  I think it might be Linda's fault.  Updating my journal was a way of getting attention and now I get all the attention I need from Linda.  :-)<br /><br />We spent a whooping four plus days together.  Friday night to Wednesday morning.  Saturday we went to a party that my friend Eric was playing for.  Went as one of the groupies since we didn't know anyone.  Found myself happily sitting with Linda listening to Eric and his band.  Maybe I should have mingled more, but eh.  At the end of the party we went down to the beach to watch the Quincy fireworks display.  <br /><br />I didn't think I could be impressed by fireworks anymore, but it was different this time, because I had Linda sitting next to me and my best friend Eric sitting next to her.  I guess things are just better when spent with people you Love.<br /><br />Sunday was spent sleeping in and building with LEGO.  I got a lot done on the river scape I'm building for Brick Blast.  Can't remember doing much else.  During the day that is.  Wink Wink nudge nudge.<br /><br />Monday I had to work so Linda stayed home and slightly annoyed my roommate with the sound of Lego.  She didn't get as much built as she had hoped.  But she was a real sweetie and did some cleaning while I was gone.  :-D<br /><br />Tuesday we spent the whole day building lego.  Made some huge progress on the landscaping and Linda got the first two floors of her building done.<br /><br />I wonder what it will be like after Brick Blast when I have less lego projects to build.  We might actually have to find something to do outside.  Heaven forbid.  ;-)
</description>
<comments>http://legostud.livejournal.com/10755.html</comments>
<lj:security>public</lj:security>
</item>
-
	<item>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://legostud.livejournal.com/10720.html</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2006 17:34:46 GMT</pubDate>
<title>The Dungeon of Love</title>
<link>http://legostud.livejournal.com/10720.html</link>
-
	<description>
I did my own dungeon today:<br /><br />Fun messages:<br />1. You find yourself in a circular crypt. You notice a chiselled epitaph to women.<br />2. You are in a dusty pit. You hear the sound of hugs in the distance.<br />3. You find yourself in a candlelit burial chamber. Scrolls about women have been pinned to the walls.<br />4. You are in a narrow fountain room. Rich tapestries illustrate hugs.<br />5. You are in a dark crypt. A plaque on the wall mentions smiling.<br />6. You find yourself in a pentagonal temple. Across one wall is a faded fresco of dragons.<br />7. You are in a crumbling fissure. You notice some graffiti about cuddling.<br /><br /><div style="background-color:#555; color:#eee; padding:8px 16px;border:8px #000 outset; width:60%; font-family:helvetica, sans-serif; text-align:center"><h3 style="color:#fe0; background-color:#777; padding:8px; margin:0px">I escaped from the Dungeon of Legostud!</h3><p>I killed Purrmeow the kobold and Mixedborder the giant spider.</p><p>I looted  the Amulet of Games, the Armour of Pizza, the Dagger of Theater, the Sword of Volleyball, the Armour of Flirting, the Axe of Lhasa Apsos, the Armour of Macgyvette, the Wand of Lego, the Dagger of Dancing and 35 gold pieces.</p><p style="color:#fe0; background-color:#777; padding:8px">Score: <b>60</b></p><a href="http://thesurrealist.co.uk/dungeon?user=legostud" style="color:#fe0;">Explore the Dungeon of Legostud</a> and try to beat this score,<br>or enter your username to generate and explore your own dungeon...<form action="http://thesurrealist.co.uk/dungeon" method="get"><input type="text" name="user" style="background: #fff url(http://stat.livejournal.com/img/userinfo.gif) no-repeat scroll 0px 1px; padding-left: 18px; color: rgb(0, 0, 204); font-weight: bold;"><input type="submit" value="Go"></form></div>
</description>
<comments>http://legostud.livejournal.com/10720.html</comments>
<lj:security>public</lj:security>
</item>
-
	<item>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://legostud.livejournal.com/10489.html</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2006 16:14:30 GMT</pubDate>
<title>My Girl Friends got a killer wand.</title>
<link>http://legostud.livejournal.com/10489.html</link>
-
	<description>
I played Macgyvette's dungeon today and picked up the Wand of Balticon.  Zap, your dead.  much fun.<br /><br /><div style="background-color:#555; color:#eee; padding:8px 16px;border:8px #000 outset; width:60%; font-family:helvetica, sans-serif; text-align:center"><h3 style="color:#fe0; background-color:#777; padding:8px; margin:0px">I escaped from the Dungeon of Macgyvette!</h3><p>I killed Tigerbright the floating eye, Jolhoeft the rat, Pyrogus the gelatinous cube, Flagster the kobold, Burningriver the floating eye, Donnad the giant spider, Been There the mind flayer, C1 the fire elemental and Seepingbrain the dragon.</p><p>I looted  the Amulet of Elaine Brennan, a Figurine of Xrsblu, the Amulet of Roozle, the Axe of Quiddler, the Sword of Djkangal, the Wand of Balticon, the Sword of Srv and 201 gold pieces.</p><p style="color:#fe0; background-color:#777; padding:8px">Score: <b>301</b></p><a href="http://thesurrealist.co.uk/dungeon?user=Macgyvette" style="color:#fe0;">Explore the Dungeon of Macgyvette</a> and try to beat this score,<br>or enter your username to generate and explore your own dungeon...<form action="http://thesurrealist.co.uk/dungeon" method="get"><input type="text" name="user" style="background: #fff url(http://stat.livejournal.com/img/userinfo.gif) no-repeat scroll 0px 1px; padding-left: 18px; color: rgb(0, 0, 204); font-weight: bold;"><input type="submit" value="Go"></form></div>
</description>
<comments>http://legostud.livejournal.com/10489.html</comments>
<lj:security>public</lj:security>
</item>
-
	<item>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://legostud.livejournal.com/10223.html</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2006 15:20:14 GMT</pubDate>
<title>#$%*^ *#)$* @(^&^</title>
<link>http://legostud.livejournal.com/10223.html</link>
-
	<description>
I just overwrote one of the web page I've been working on for awhile.  Man am I pissed off now.<br /><br />Granted the page wasn't working correctly anyways, but still I would have like to have kept it as a backup.  So now I have to try and remember what I did to the original page to make it into the new one.  So many if statements and section loops.  I think I'm going to lose my mind.<br /><br />Must work on something else for awhile or I'm going to scream.
</description>
<comments>http://legostud.livejournal.com/10223.html</comments>
<lj:mood>pissed off</lj:mood>
<lj:security>public</lj:security>
</item>
-
	<item>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://legostud.livejournal.com/9855.html</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2006 03:03:31 GMT</pubDate>
<title>Dreams</title>
<link>http://legostud.livejournal.com/9855.html</link>
-
	<description>
I'm getting more and more comfortable around Linda.  We've now hit the point where we can spend the night with out fooling around.  We're still goofy and silly at night, but I'm hoping that doesn't disappear.<br /><br />Yesterday I picked up Linda at the T station and she had a bump hat with her.  I laughed.  <br /><br />Sunday night we whacked heads pretty hard.  So hard that her teeth hurt and I ended up with a splitting headache Monday morning.  So this was just the best gag.  She even beat me to the punch, because I was planning on wearing my bike helmet to bed.<br /><br />I love how goofy we are.<br /><br />During my sleep last night I had the weirdest dreams.  It is a very long dream full of odd transitions.  Maybe you can find some meaning to it.  I'm sure there is some.<br /><a name="cutid1"></a><br /><br />It started out with me (as a woman) apologizing to my friend (don't know who he was) about not noticing the third crocodile.  To which he responded not too worry and handed me a 9mm to take care of this crocodile.  <br /><br />As I'm searching under a parked car on the dense residential street that I'm standing on, A motor home comes around the corner with its side door open.  Two pairs of sneakers fall out onto the street.  I put down my gun on the car and walked over to pick them up.  On the way to pick them up, I realized it probably wasn't a smart idea to leave my gun on the car.<br /><br />Sure enough a little boy has jumped out of the motor home and is playing with it.  He then takes a bullet out of the gun, drops the weapon and hops back into the motor home.  I run after the boy fearing he's going to hurt himself.<br /><br />As the motor home starts to drive off, I dive through the open door and land inside.  No one has noticed I'm there so I mentioned that I have their sneakers.  They don't seem to care.  I tell them that their son has taken one of my bullets.  They seem angry.  As I turn in frustration, I find a man in a bath robe.  He tires suggesting that I was required to give him pleasure since I was trespassing (or something like that).  Remember, I'm still a woman at this point.  He goes as far as to open his robe before I totally lose it.<br /><br />In my anger, I point out to the family that the inside of their motor home is going to be real attractive when it is covered by a fine mist of red when the bullet blows off their son's head.  I then grab the little kid and shout at him to tell me where the bullet is.  Man did I yell at him.  Must of scared the crap out of him.<br /><br />This is finally enough to loosen his tongue, because he tells me where his stash is.  Under the driver's seat.  There we find a large gallon bag full of water and nails.  His Mom puts the back to her mouth and tips it back.  I can see the nails floating towards her, but the water isn't coming out.  Very odd.<br /><br />I take the bag from her and go outside.  There, I pour the bag onto the ground.  Not the smartest idea as the contents go everywhere.  I kneel down to try and find the bullet, but can't.  I even look under the motor home into a deep hole which is partially made of Lego. <br /><br />The scene then changes as my friend Eric walks in.  I'm now myself again, but now I'm in an office building.  I'm still on my knees, but with a hammer in my hands.  Gary (the VP of operations at work) is sitting at a desk near me.  Eric walks over to Gary and says something inappropriate to Gary (Eric was laid off by Gary Friday).  This something relates to the fact that Gary wanted to say goodbye to Eric before he left and didn't get the chance (actually happened).<br /><br />I get really pissed off at Eric for being so immature.  I almost hit him with the hammer.  Instead I decide to face him and ask what the hell is wrong.  I walk through the doorway and look for him.  Man does he walk fast.  I find him at the other end of the room talking to someone.  When I get there he's sitting on the couch and so am I.  I ask him why he's upset and if it has to do with being laided off.<br /><br />He admits to me that he is really s
ad that he got laid off.  I give him a hug to comfort him.  At which point the sofa changes to the car seats in the Tracker I used to own and we're now slowly driving up a long hill.  The engine has just enough torque to move the vehicle without stalling.<br /><br />I then start to drive the vehicle.  I find an intersection that looks somewhat familiar to a place in a previous dream that night and try to head back to the hotel.  There are lots of highways signs and it is very confusing.  <br /><br />As we take the turn that should lead us to the hotel, the car vanishes and we're now walking along a path.  And Eric is now Linda.  I've also acquired a bag of apples.  I notice them only because I drop one and it rolls away.  <br /><br />We continue around the bend and see a crossing gate.  There are several people here waiting for the gate to go up.  The gate goes up and we start moving, but the gate comes back down again.  Apparently some kid pushed the crossing button.  Several people are upset with him.  I know who it is too.  As I'm scowling at him, I drop another apple, which rolls over to him.  He smiles back at the gift.<br /><br />The gate finally goes up and we continue down the path.  The people around me turn into NELUG members and the path becomes a hallway.  I see Teddy (Nelug member in charge of the moon base display for Brick Blast) and leave Linda to tell him of my inappropriate design for one of the modules.<br /><br />At this point Teddy and I both realize that we're alone now.  Where did everyone go?  We turn back and follow the hallway back to a set of restroom doors.  They must be in there.<br /><br />I turn and notice that we're in a bar.  At first it is the seedy beer only type, but as I look harder I see the foo foo drinks at another bar.  Teddy tells me what he wants, but I can't remember what he says.  So he repeats it again.  Still nothing.  So he tells the waitress who is standing on the bar next to him.  I then tell her I want Peach Schnapes on the rocks.  To which she replies jokingly "Peach Schnapes on the Socks" and walks away.  <br /><br />Teddy pulls out his wallet to find some money and his wallet falls apart.  Little pieces fly towards me which I pick up while he's picking up the main part that has fallen into the hallway.  Someone steps on it before he can grab it though.  <br /><br />There is then a debate between Teddy, this person and the owner as to who owns the wallet.  The owner is leaning towards the thief so I try to vouch for Teddy and point out that I have the other parts of the wallet, but they don't care.<br /><br />I then realize that there are pictures in the wallet of me.  So I sit down next to the thief and pull out some 8.5 x 11 photos from the wallet (dreams don't always make sense).  I find one of a Suburban Adventure Club party (club I use to belong to) where we were all wearing costumes.  Teddy must have taken the picture.  I then find a picture of Teddy taking a picture of his and a friends reflection in a Cafe window.  Solid evidence that the wallet is Teddy's so I turn and walk away with the wallet.<br /><br />As I turn the bar becomes a run down street and the wallet becomes a homework assignment.  The assignment that I have is to build a sidewalk and a patio for this decrepit building.  Linda shows up and says don't worry, I'm good with water damage.  I smile and wake up.<br /><br />Hows that for wierd?
</description>
<comments>http://legostud.livejournal.com/9855.html</comments>
<category>dreams</category>
<category>linda</category>
<lj:mood>sleepy</lj:mood>
<lj:security>public</lj:security>
</item>
-
	<item>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://legostud.livejournal.com/9612.html</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2006 02:21:44 GMT</pubDate>
<title>Empty Pockets</title>
<link>http://legostud.livejournal.com/9612.html</link>
-
	<description>
I did my finances and found out that from June 2005 to June 2006 I spent $1k more than I made.  Not the greatest of things to find out, but also not too big a number to deal with.  Turns out I have an extra $600 a month to spend on LEGO or Luxuries over my base expenses.  So if I can figure out how to spend just $300 a month, I'll be in good shape.  Right now I'm spending $600 so I need to cut something out.<br /><br />I still have a few tricks to reduce my base expenses too.  The Insurance bill can go down if I reduce the coverage on the Honda, maybe the JEEP as well.  The Car Expenses can go down if I start biking more; need to get some rain gear.  The Food expense can go down if I can start making my own meals instead of ordering out or buying premade (including some snacks).<br /><br />I also have a pile of stuff to sell on E-bay so that might help as well.
</description>
<comments>http://legostud.livejournal.com/9612.html</comments>
<category>expenses</category>
<lj:mood>Thoughtful</lj:mood>
<lj:security>public</lj:security>
</item>
-
	<item>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://legostud.livejournal.com/9343.html</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2006 04:12:36 GMT</pubDate>
<title>Lonelyness</title>
<link>http://legostud.livejournal.com/9343.html</link>
-
	<description>
Just watched <i>The Last Samurai</i> and now my emotions are very overwhelming.  It is during these times that the emotional side of my brain gains control over my logical side.  It is during these times that I truly feel.<br /><br />What I feel now is loneliness.  I miss Linda so much.  <br /><br />I started thinking about how much I want her to be in my life.  To see her smile when I wake up in the morning.....  I miss that smile already.  To have her wrap her arms around me and make the whole world just disappear.<br /><br />Tonight, I thought about marrying her, but the logical side wouldn't let me think about it for very long.  Too many unknowns.  Besides, I haven't had a chance to meet her parents.  Let alone ask her Dad's permission.  ;-)<br /><br />Then I started remembering that I wasn't going to build expectations for this relationship.  That I was just going to go with it.  Let the wind take it where it will. Hopefully it will survive the test of time, but if not, I'm only 31 and I still have time.<br /><br />This thought actually pissed me off.  I don't want to look for someone else.  I Love Linda.  I don't even want to think about someone else.<br /><br />I wish she could move in with me, but it just won't work right now.  I've got too many bills right now to support her as well.  I need to look at my finances again.  Maybe there is way some how.  Maybe it's time to find a job that actually pays what I'm worth.  Maybe my boss will give me the bonus I keep asking for.  Maybe I should get off my ass and make some money on the side.<br /><br />I'm hoping for a nice bonus as a reward for saving Dancing Deer a ton of money.  For 6+ months, I filled in as the Creative Services person on top of my own job.  While being Salary.  So what I've asked my boss for is part of the Salary that Dancing Deer would have paid a Creative Services person if we had hired some one.  Seems only fare since I did the job for so long and during my busiest time period.  Hell, I'm still being asked to do odd jobs.<br /><br />I'm starting to feel better now.  I still miss Linda though.  I think it is time I find a Teddy Bear version of Linda to cuddle with when she's not here.  :-)
</description>
<comments>http://legostud.livejournal.com/9343.html</comments>
<lj:security>public</lj:security>
</item>
-
	<item>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://legostud.livejournal.com/9201.html</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2006 23:28:59 GMT</pubDate>
<title>mmmmmmmmmmmmmmm.</title>
<link>http://legostud.livejournal.com/9201.html</link>
-
	<description>
Just had one of the best weekends ever with Linda.  It always seems to be that way with Linda around.  ;-)  <br /><br />I'm feeling really groovy right now.  <br /><br />I'll try skipping on the details, because I'm very tired from last night.  Wink Wink, Nudge Nudge.  <br /><br />Quick version of this weekend.  Ready?<br /><br />Friday<br />1. Cooked supper<br />2. Worked on Lego bridge for Brick Blast<br />3. Fooled around<br />4. Tried to sleep, but couldn't get comfortable<br />5. Woke up like wicked early (6:30am)<br />6. Linda wore a very attractive outfit<br />7. Built with Lego for the Millyard project<br />8. Had fun goofing around with Linda at the Millyard<br />9. Went to a party at a former co-workers<br />10. Wasn't allowed to drink the pretty foo foo drinks :-(<br />11. Went to bed and again couldn't really sleep<br />12. Saw Linda off to go to the Millyard<br />13. Took a long nap until noon<br />14. Went shopping for a weed whacker, Lego and doggie bags.  Got all but the Lego. :-(<br />15. Mowed the lawn<br />16. Built more of the Lego bridge<br />17. Cooked Linda supper<br />18. More Lego<br />19. Way too much fooling around.  Very proud of 1.5 hours. :-)<br />20. Got some good sleep, but not enough. <br />Monday
</description>
<comments>http://legostud.livejournal.com/9201.html</comments>
<lj:security>public</lj:security>
</item>
-
	<item>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://legostud.livejournal.com/8850.html</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2006 10:44:55 GMT</pubDate>
<title>Tear in my eye</title>
<link>http://legostud.livejournal.com/8850.html</link>
-
	<description>
I woke up in the middle night to find myself sleeping on Linda's side of the bed.  My neck hurt from her puffier pillow so I rolled back on to my side.  It wasn't as comfortable, except the pillow.<br /><br />When I woke again in the morning, I started thinking about "Linda's side".  I've never had a Linda's side of the bed before.  I then started to picture Linda sleeping there.  I stretched out my arm and caressed the sheets.  Tears formed in my eyes (still are 30 min later), because she wasn't there.<br /><br />Today, I miss Linda.
</description>
<comments>http://legostud.livejournal.com/8850.html</comments>
<lj:security>public</lj:security>
</item>
-
	<item>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://legostud.livejournal.com/8698.html</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2006 01:15:06 GMT</pubDate>
<title>Seeking the Ground</title>
<link>http://legostud.livejournal.com/8698.html</link>
-
	<description>
My mind has been restless since this weekend.  Linda said something Friday night that I still haven't been able to shake off.  She's worried that one of these days I might wake up and realize that I'm in Love with being in a relationship and not in Love with Linda.<br /><br />Am I?  This just keeps going through my head over and over.<br /><br /><a name="cutid1"></a><br />I really do like telling people that I'm seeing someone.  This is the first time in my life that I've been able to do this.  So many new opportunities are now available to me because I'm seeing someone. <br /><br />I also like Linda as well.  There are so many things about her that I like.  Problem is that she isn't what I fantasized about.  In my dreams it was always the young 20 year old with the hot body.  We'd do these sexy things in public and wear sexy clothing.  Linda is someone else.  Someone who is more than a fantasy.  Someone who I could see myself having a real relationship with not just a fling.  <br /><br />I'm no longer the 20 something in the fantasies either.  I'm older now.  I'm actually a little bored with sex too.  Hate to say that though.<br /><br />I think it is time that I gave up the fantasy.  It's hard and depressing to think that I may never do these things.  Then again maybe Linda will surprise me.  She said she's going to wear a dress Saturday to the party so I might end up not having to give it up.<br /><br /><br />Another issue I'm dealing with is why I don't miss Linda when she leaves.  I think about her constantly, but I don't miss her.  I think it might be because of Cassie.  Before I got Cassie, I would cry myself to sleep, because I was so lonely.  I haven't done that once since I adopted her.<br /><br />I think I've figured it out.  I've got so much human interaction everyday that I couldn't imagine myself having more.  I have Cassie (not human, but requires a lot of attention), my roommate, my parents and at least three people at work who are constantly coming to me for help.  I'm burnt out with people.<br /><br />I need a vacation.<br /><br /><a name="cutid2"></a>Brick Blast is in the way and will most likely tax me.  Then I there is Brickfest, which I really want to go to, because so many NELUGers are going this year.  So July and August seem booked for vacation.  However I might be able to stretch out the Brickfest trip to include a tour of Washington DC.  <br /><br />What I really want for a vacation is to drive somewhere like San Diego.  When I'm driving on a road trip with someone, maybe Linda, I'm in heaven.  I hadn't realized this until just now.    Now I just have to find a good time to take a vacation.  That's unlikely to happen anytime soon.  Sadly, It may not happen until next year, because September is the time I prepare for the months of hell, October to December.<br /><br />I really do like being a hermit sometimes.  ;-)  Maybe I should take up camping, that could be fun.
</description>
<comments>http://legostud.livejournal.com/8698.html</comments>
<lj:security>public</lj:security>
</item>
-
	<item>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://legostud.livejournal.com/8226.html</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2006 04:13:33 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NELUG and Linda on the brain</title>
<link>http://legostud.livejournal.com/8226.html</link>
-
	<description>
NELUG is ramping up for Brick Blast coming up in July and it is starting to take up more and more of my time.  A lot of it is being spent trying to keep things moving in a productive direction.  The rest is trying really hard to articulate what I'm thinking.  How do I translate this really cool image in my head into text.  Or do I spend more time trying to draw it out.<br /><br />And of course the biggest issue is that Brick Blast is taking time away from being silly with Linda.  I have to find a good medium.<br /><br />Took a nap today.  Came home from work around 5pm and fell asleep on the sofa.  Cassie woke me up at one point, but then I fell asleep again.  Woke up again and found an empty apartment, no Cassie.  Apparently my folks ate supper without me.  Even took Cassie downstairs.  <br /><br />They called my cell phone, but it was in the car.  I don't get why they didn't call my name when they got Cassie.  That usually wakes me.  So I had to reheat supper.  It also meant that I didn't get to spend time with them talking over dinner.  I wanted to know how their trip went and share about Linda.  <br /><br />I'm getting a weird vibe from them about Linda.  They're not all, what's she like.  More the oh that's nice attitude.  It's a little odd, especially because I want to tell everyone about her.<br /><br />I told my best friend yesterday.  He was really happy for me.  He's been wanting me to meet someone more than I have.  He's been waiting for my Loving and caring side to find an outlet.  Boy did I find one too.<br /><br />Linda I'm about to make your head spin again so I hope you're sitting down.  ;-)<br /><br />Friends are asking me for details about Linda and this what I'm going to tell them.<br /><br />Linda is this wonderful woman who accepts me for who I am.  There have been many times when I've said something and thought, damn that was stupid.  Instead of being offend and leaving, Linda just says "you know if you had said X that would have been better".  I Love that about her.  She knows that I really care about her and if I say something that doesn't fit, it probably means I simply said something stupid.  There's no story with her.  No "what did he mean by that".  <br /><br />There is also this feeling when I'm with her that I've known her for a long time.  Almost like in a past life.  I've never been this comfortable around someone before.  It is also the little things that I've been noticing as well.  When we were at the Millyard we stopped gabbing while we were working.  I would have been annoyed if she had want to gab while I was concentrating, but she didn't.  I didn't even notice it at the time, because it felt so natural.  Just like when my brother and I are working on something.<br /><br />We also compliment each other physically.  She's soft and I'm bony so when we hug we just meld as one.  I really like that.  I could stay in her arms forever.<br /><br />Then there is her smile.  A few years ago, I created a Match.com profile, well tried to, and it asked me to fill out a section on what body type I was interested in.  I looked at the photos, but could never narrow it down.  What I realized was that I was picky the photos with the best smiles.  What I find most attractive about someone is their smile and Linda has this.  To me she is the most attractive person I've ever met. <br /><br />Then there is her laugh.  Combine that with a great smile and you have someone who is truly happy.  I find it really hard to be anything but happy when I'm around her.<br /><br />Of course now, I've probably said too much.  Probably made Linda blush, but I like doing that.<br /><br />If things keep going the way they are, I can see a beautiful future.  I wonder how long you have to be dating or how comfortable you need to be before asking someone to live with you.  I know it's too soon now, but something I'll have to think about.
</description>
<comments>http://legostud.livejournal.com/8226.html</comments>
<category>nelug</category>
<category>linda</category>
<lj:mood>cheerful</lj:mood>
<lj:security>public</lj:security>
</item>
-
	<item>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://legostud.livejournal.com/8096.html</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2006 05:21:58 GMT</pubDate>
<title>Still awake</title>
<link>http://legostud.livejournal.com/8096.html</link>
-
	<description>
I am soooo tired.  I took an hour and a half nap.  Most of me woke up again, but I feel like something hasn't.  My stomach definitely didn't like the nap.  <br /><br />Flight is supposed to land at 1:30am.<br /><br />I can't wait for my folks to call so I can get this nightmare over with.
</description>
<comments>http://legostud.livejournal.com/8096.html</comments>
<lj:security>public</lj:security>
</item>
-
	<item>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://legostud.livejournal.com/7913.html</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2006 02:53:28 GMT</pubDate>
<title>Long night</title>
<link>http://legostud.livejournal.com/7913.html</link>
-
	<description>
I'm getting so tired, but I can't go to bed.  I promised to pick up my folks at the airport tonight.  Well actually tomorrow now.  Their flight was supposed to arrive at 9pm and now it's arriving at 12:00am. Ugh.  I'm going to be suffering at work tomorrow.
</description>
<comments>http://legostud.livejournal.com/7913.html</comments>
<lj:security>public</lj:security>
</item>
-
	<item>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://legostud.livejournal.com/7482.html</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2006 01:59:13 GMT</pubDate>
<title>Feeling Icky</title>
<link>http://legostud.livejournal.com/7482.html</link>
-
	<description>
Cassie's tummy is upset.  Not sure what's up, but she keeps having minor erking.<br /><br />I'm hoping it isn't from the antifreeze.  I might have spilt some on the floor when I was trying to wash her booster seat.  Hope not.  :-(<br /><br />Hopefully she'll be feeling better tomorrow.
</description>
<comments>http://legostud.livejournal.com/7482.html</comments>
<lj:security>public</lj:security>
</item>
-
	<item>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://legostud.livejournal.com/7301.html</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2006 22:54:47 GMT</pubDate>
<title>My Brain Hurts</title>
<link>http://legostud.livejournal.com/7301.html</link>
-
	<description>
I'm like wicked exhausted, but now it is from over exposure to the sun and not sleep deprivation (10+ hours).  <br /><br />My skin feels like it is burnt, but I put sun screen on.  It isn't pink, but it tingles.  Oh and I forgot to protect my ears again. Oops<br /><br />Today I spent 4 hours in the parking lot at work painting lines.  It looks great.  I even tried my hand at painting a handicap symbol.  Not sure how well that space is going to be accepted, but I felt it needed to be done.  I'm worried that co-workers might see it as a waste, but we do have one disabled person working for us.<br /><br />Can't wait until Tuesday to see if my co-workers accept it.  This uncertainty is annoying.<br /><br />Thought about asking <span class='ljuser' lj:user='macgyvette' style='white-space: nowrap;'><a href='http://macgyvette.livejournal.com/profile'><img src='http://stat.livejournal.com/img/userinfo.gif' alt='[info]' width='17' height='17' style='vertical-align: bottom; border: 0;' /></a><a href='http://macgyvette.livejournal.com/'><b>macgyvette</b></a></span> to come paint lines, but kept forgetting.  Thought about it on the highway going to Home Depot, forgot when I got there.  Thought about it on the way to work, but forgot when I got there.  Thought about it when I started painting lines, but didn't feel like it anymore.  I just wanted to finish at that point.  I'll write her an email when I'm done.  Hopefully I'll remember. ;-)<br /><br />While I was painting, I found a icky mess in the back of the Jeep.  The antifreeze bottle got squished and leaked out on to the floor.  Thankfully Jeep carpeting is designed for easy removal and washing.  Too bad the rest of the stuff in the back wasn't.  Like Cassie's boaster seat.  That might be a lost cause now. :-(<br /><br />Cassie was back to normal when I came home.  Was jumping up and trying to play with me, but I still had antifreeze on my hands so I couldn't touch her.  <br /><br /><span class='ljuser' lj:user='mixedborder' style='white-space: nowrap;'><a href='http://mixedborder.livejournal.com/profile'><img src='http://stat.livejournal.com/img/userinfo.gif' alt='[info]' width='17' height='17' style='vertical-align: bottom; border: 0;' /></a><a href='http://mixedborder.livejournal.com/'><b>mixedborder</b></a></span> told me he had cuddled and played with her while I was out; which was really nice.  I think she needed it.<br /><br />Played a game of Quiddler with <span class='ljuser' lj:user='mixedborder' style='white-space: nowrap;'><a href='http://mixedborder.livejournal.com/profile'><img src='http://stat.livejournal.com/img/userinfo.gif' alt='[info]' width='17' height='17' style='vertical-align: bottom; border: 0;' /></a><a href='http://mixedborder.livejournal.com/'><b>mixedborder</b></a></span>.  I barely beat him (280 to 279), but only because he was being nice and not making me take points off for misspelled words.  I think I need to read the dictionary now.<br /><br />Now I'm thinking about falling asleep.  I should be thinking about what I'm going to do tomorrow though.  I was thinking it would be nice to go kayaking with my brother, but I'm just too tired to think right now.
</description>
<comments>http://legostud.livejournal.com/7301.html</comments>
<lj:security>public</lj:security>
</item>
-
	<item>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://legostud.livejournal.com/7126.html</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2006 03:34:40 GMT</pubDate>
<title>A beautiful day</title>
<link>http://legostud.livejournal.com/7126.html</link>
-
	<description>
This will be my first entry just for friends.  However I'm still leaving stuff out.<br /><br />I just spent a wonderful time with Linda, (details below).  Now I'm really tired from all this activity.  My eyes are having trouble staying open right now so tonight I plan on recharging.  Should be able to sleep in too, since Cassie was walked late tonight.  If the post is a little off, it's probably because I'm half asleep.<br /><br />I'm starting to wonder if Cassie is jealous of Linda.  She seems a little depressed, since she isn't bugging me to play with her or cuddle.  She's actually been very well behaved.<br /><br />Work reared its ugly head a few of times while I was with Linda.  I had to fix the home page to link to the spreading sweetness site.  Then Ursula called in the morning looking for information.  Lastly while eating dinner she called again to let me know that she had the winners ready to post to the site (planned event so no biggy).  It just bugged me a little bit that work got mixed in with the worlds longest second date (28 hours).<br /><br />Hopefully Linda will come over again.  I'm not sure I want a sleep over on a weeknight though since I'm not sure I'd be very productive the next day at work.  However the thought of going another week without seeing her is tough.<br /><br />Last nights details (or what I'm willing to share):<br />It started last night when I picked her up early, but late as well.  The original plan was to meet at 5:30, but work said I could leave at 4 instead of five so we moved it up to 4:30.  Then Ursula dropped an ASAP project in my lap just before I was going to leave so I didn't leave until 4:40.  So early and late at the same time.<br /><br />From her house we went to the food store near my house to buy some food to cook up.  Felt weird to go to the grocery store to only buy three things, steak, frozen peas and a box of pasta, but that's all I needed.  <br /><br />We talked over a nice simple meal.  I took care of the cooking and cleaning.  Linda wanted to help, but I couldn't think of a way so she watched and talked while I prepared supper.  I think I did a good job too.  The meat was a little chewy though.  I'll have to try a different cut next time.<br /><br />Once supper was done and the dishes were cleaned we curled up on the sofa to watch "Life of Brain".  The media center couldn't detect it for some reason so we watch the "Holy Grail" instead.  Surprisingly enough, it was much funnier this time because I was watching it with Linda.<br /><br />Then, well I'm not telling what.<br /><br />After that we tried to fall asleep, but we just kept making each other laugh.  Even after agreeing to go to sleep, Linda would giggle every now and then.  It took a lot of will power for me not to giggle as well.<br /><br />Morning came way to early (8pm).  My stomach was hungry (this happened a lot) so we got up and had breakfast.  I shared some of my cereal with her and a banana.  She was still tired so she went back to bed afterwards while I took Cassie for a walk.<br /><br />I was a little tired as well so after the walk I went up stairs.  I didn't actually get to sleep though.  Did something else.<br /><br />Earthfest was on the schedule for the day, but it just felt like it was going to rain so we stayed home instead.  She showed me a new game called Quiddler.  Much fun.  Object of the game is to make words from the cards your dealt.  I did very well and annoyed Linda.  Apparently, I shouldn't play poker.  Every time I got a good hand or a card I wanted I would get all happy.  This happened a lot and I won most of the matches.<br /><br />While we were playing, Linda suggested maybe we should do something outside of the house.  During our walk to the Sub shop for lunch I noticed Ice Age 2 was playing at the capital.  I suggested this and we walked down.<br /><br />Ice Age 2 is mainly about Manny the Mammoth falling in love with a possum.  Well actually a Mammoth raised by possums.  It was a good romantic comedy.<br /><br />The movie ended around supper time so I suggested an Italian pl
ace near by.  When we got there it was closed.  This has happened every time I've want to eat there.  So plan B, we went to the Arlington Diner instead.  She ordered a chicken salad sandwich and I ordered the chicken cutlet.  Man was there a lot of food.  I'm all set now for tomorrow's lunch and supper.<br /><br />It was late after supper so I took Linda home.  I wouldn't have minded having her stay another night.  I know I wouldn't have any trouble falling asleep tonight.  Other things would have been tougher.
</description>
<comments>http://legostud.livejournal.com/7126.html</comments>
<category>linda</category>
<category>private</category>
<lj:mood>Too tired</lj:mood>
<lj:security>usemask</lj:security>
</item>
-
	<item>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://legostud.livejournal.com/6772.html</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2006 18:18:08 GMT</pubDate>
<title>Nucking Futs</title>
<link>http://legostud.livejournal.com/6772.html</link>
-
	<description>
I'm going Nucking Futs sitting here at work.  Way too much s*&# needs to get done and no where near enough time.<br /><br />What ticks me off more is that the pres is trying to get people to volunteer to work on Saturday.  Hah, why would I want to volunteer to hand out cookies.  If I'm not getting paid, piss off.<br /><br />Yes I'm in one of my over stressed moods.  I need to find a way to relax.  I know how about biking home down Mass Ave.  That should be relaxing, not.  Of course this extra stress may help me break my speed record.  :-0
</description>
<comments>http://legostud.livejournal.com/6772.html</comments>
<lj:security>public</lj:security>
</item>
-
	<item>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://legostud.livejournal.com/6547.html</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2006 01:30:38 GMT</pubDate>
<title>Now where was I.</title>
<link>http://legostud.livejournal.com/6547.html</link>
-
	<description>
**Warning the following message is very long**<br /><br />It's been one of those weeks where everything feels like it has to be done now.  I'm feeling very compressed.  Hopefully I won't explode.  However, my arm did go numb today at work from over using the mouse.<br /><br />I'm trying to rewrite a shipping algorithm include file for work.  The developer is a little weak when it comes to logic and I'm anything but so this file has been driving me crazy ever since I first saw it.  I've got most of it working now, but I can't get it to adjust the shipping times for holidays.  It's been very annoying try to debug it.<br /><br />Also got caught being forgetful.  I forgot to check for HSN orders on Friday and Monday.  I found them on Tuesday and they were were supposed to ship Monday.  Oops.  Oh well, I would have just bit someone head off about how over worked I am if they had pressed the issue.<br /><br />I think I'm starting to get my brain away from work, but I still have one more issue to vent.  Why do the people at work have to park like they're on crack.  I've seem some really bad parking lately.  They park at angles, leave too much space between each other, park along the back row so it is harder to get to the front row and block everyone in by parking across the entrance.  Bunch of inconsiderate F&$*'n morons.  This Monday, I've decided to paint parking lines.  I'm tired of it.  <br /><br />The suck part of painting lines is that I'm not going to get paid to do it.  I'm also required to take Monday as one of my PTO days, because it's a holiday.  Stupid system.  I might not go in, but I don't see a better time to paint it.  I'll just work a little less during the week (come in later).<br /><br />Ok I feel better, work is drifting into the background and <span class='ljuser' lj:user='macgyvette' style='white-space: nowrap;'><a href='http://macgyvette.livejournal.com/profile'><img src='http://stat.livejournal.com/img/userinfo.gif' alt='[info]' width='17' height='17' style='vertical-align: bottom; border: 0;' /></a><a href='http://macgyvette.livejournal.com/'><b>macgyvette</b></a></span> is filling my thoughts again.  I need a good nickname for her.  Using these LJ user tags are annoying.  Maybe this weekend we'll come up with something.  <br /><br />Her lips on mine, her smile and seeing her glowing were the highlights of last night.  <br /><br />Had a NELUG meeting last night.  I told her before hand to keep "us" a secret during the meeting.  I wasn't quite ready to tell them.  Then she came into the restaurant and all I wanted to do was go over and give her a big hug.  Would have too if I wasn't trapped in the corner.<br /><br />It was a good meeting.  I sat next to Wayne and Dave who I really like.  Wayne usually acts like a kid, because he has to be grown up all the time at home and work.  Dave and I just think alike.  Well, he thinks a little more about Lego than I do.  So I had good conversations about Brikwars, Lego, Food and Grandma with Midgets porn.  Dave told a story about porn that we all laughed at.  <br /><br />Got to see the new NXT system.  The designer must have been really horny when he came up with it though.  The motor looks like a penis and the touch sensor looks like a nipple.  Oh and get this the touch sensors are <i>more sensitive</i> to the touch too.  I almost laughed at the thought.  Of course it could just be me that has the dirty mind.  On that note, maybe it should be called the new mind<i>porn</i> sets.  :-)<br /><br />I also gave Eijah a ride up there.  He's a nice kid.  I had forgot what I was like at 18.  It's been so long.  He's a geek like me so we were able to talk on the way up to the meeting.  Well more like shout over the loud Jeep.<br /><br />After the meeting something cool happened.  Elijah got a ride home from his folks.  This meant I could spend the entire ride home with <span class='ljuser' lj:user='macgyvette' style='white-space: nowrap;'><a href='http://macgyvette.livejournal.com/profile'><img src='http://stat.livejournal.com/img/userinfo.gif' alt='[info]' width='17' heig
ht='17' style='vertical-align: bottom; border: 0;' /></a><a href='http://macgyvette.livejournal.com/'><b>macgyvette</b></a></span>.  She was tired so I did most of the talking.  Made her laugh so many times.  I think I scared her once too.  It's her fault though she said get in the left lane quickly so I did.  ;-)<br /><br />Once we got to her house she gave me a hug and a kiss that I could feel all the way home.  I was on a cloud most of the way home.  <br /><br />I mentioned on the way to her house that I'm usually good at remembering how to get somewhere.  She took this as a dig about her getting lost trying to find my place.  When I was simply trying to share something about who I am.  Oh well.<br /><br />When I was at Landmark Education, they taught me that words have no meaning.  Try reading a foreign word that you don't know.  What does it mean?  Nothing.  When we translate the word we apply a meaning to it.  It is possible for others to apply a different meaning.  What does all this mean?  Nothing so I don't let it bother me.<br /><br /><span class='ljuser' lj:user='macgyvette' style='white-space: nowrap;'><a href='http://macgyvette.livejournal.com/profile'><img src='http://stat.livejournal.com/img/userinfo.gif' alt='[info]' width='17' height='17' style='vertical-align: bottom; border: 0;' /></a><a href='http://macgyvette.livejournal.com/'><b>macgyvette</b></a></span> sent me an email Monday morning that nearly had my brain explode trying to see all the possibilities that it opened up.  She wants to come over and spend the night?!  What does that mean?  There were so many possibilities that I couldn't figure them all out.  I decided to do something brave, I said ok.<br /><br />I'm going to cook her something nice and then we can sit back and watch DVDs (or those low tech VHS tapes).  Maybe <span class='ljuser' lj:user='mixedborder' style='white-space: nowrap;'><a href='http://mixedborder.livejournal.com/profile'><img src='http://stat.livejournal.com/img/userinfo.gif' alt='[info]' width='17' height='17' style='vertical-align: bottom; border: 0;' /></a><a href='http://mixedborder.livejournal.com/'><b>mixedborder</b></a></span> will be working or spending time watching the game with a friend that night.  Hint Hint.  That way I can have some alone time with her.  He mostly stays in his room anyways so I'm not too concerned.<br /><br />I'm more concerned with falling asleep that night.  Thoughts of her are keeping me awake at night, the morning sun is waking me up early and work is sucking the energy out of me.  I could fall asleep any moment now and it's not even 9pm.
</description>
<comments>http://legostud.livejournal.com/6547.html</comments>
<lj:security>public</lj:security>
</item>
-
	<item>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://legostud.livejournal.com/6321.html</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2006 02:39:07 GMT</pubDate>
<title>I'm giving up ribbing my friends.</title>
<link>http://legostud.livejournal.com/6321.html</link>
-
	<description>
Why do people take such pleasure from ribbing someone?  This is actually a question for myself.  My brother and I have always teased each other and somewhere along the line I learned how to rib him.  Now I seem to do it to everyone I care about.  And not just the friendly do it once, but I keep at it until the other guy gets pissed off.<br /><br />I even ribbed <span class='ljuser' lj:user='macgyvette' style='white-space: nowrap;'><a href='http://macgyvette.livejournal.com/profile'><img src='http://stat.livejournal.com/img/userinfo.gif' alt='[info]' width='17' height='17' style='vertical-align: bottom; border: 0;' /></a><a href='http://macgyvette.livejournal.com/'><b>macgyvette</b></a></span> about getting lost on Saturday.  Looking back, I now see myself laughing while I torment someone I care about.  Sorry.<br /><br />I truly did enjoy it, but now I starting to wonder why on earth could this be so.  It goes against what I really believe, that my friends should be happy, so why do I do this?  Does it make them laugh?  Probably the first time, but then I keep going.  Why do I put my friends down like this?  Doesn't seem right anymore so I'm giving it up starting now.  <br /><br />I'll have to go cold turkey, if I'm going to succeed though.  Man this isn't going to be easy.  If I can get some of my friends to make me aware when I start it would help.  So consider yourself asked.<br /><br />Everyday I try to find something new about who I am.  Sometimes they're good and other times they're not.  This is a not time.<br /><br />I'm now starting to think this might be part of the reason I lost to of my best friends.  They won't even talk to me and I haven't a clue why.
</description>
<comments>http://legostud.livejournal.com/6321.html</comments>
<category>ribbing</category>
<category>friends</category>
<category>giving it up</category>
<lj:mood>wet eyes</lj:mood>
<lj:security>public</lj:security>
</item>
-
	<item>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://legostud.livejournal.com/6085.html</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2006 15:50:25 GMT</pubDate>
<title>Happy</title>
<link>http://legostud.livejournal.com/6085.html</link>
-
	<description>
I was just thinking about last night again now that I've had time to absorb it all.  What a wonderful goodbye hug.  She nearly put me to sleep in her arms.  It was so comfy.<br /><br />At the end of our date, I discovered that my brother had come over.  He apparently got confused and thought we were going to the movies that night.  oops.  We instead agreed to play Carassonne instead.  Funny thing happened to, he beat me 2 out of three games.  I blame this on <span class='ljuser' lj:user='macgyvette' style='white-space: nowrap;'><a href='http://macgyvette.livejournal.com/profile'><img src='http://stat.livejournal.com/img/userinfo.gif' alt='[info]' width='17' height='17' style='vertical-align: bottom; border: 0;' /></a><a href='http://macgyvette.livejournal.com/'><b>macgyvette</b></a></span> filling my head with wonderful distractions.  ;-)<br /><br />Today my brother is coming over and we're going to see Robin Williams' movie RV.  He said it was funny enough to see again and I'm a fan of Robin Williams. <br /><br />We're going to bike over to the theater so we'll probably get rained on on the way back, but I don't really care.<br /><br />Started thinking about future possibilities.  The main one was Brick Blast (NELUG event in June).  I'd really like for <span class='ljuser' lj:user='macgyvette' style='white-space: nowrap;'><a href='http://macgyvette.livejournal.com/profile'><img src='http://stat.livejournal.com/img/userinfo.gif' alt='[info]' width='17' height='17' style='vertical-align: bottom; border: 0;' /></a><a href='http://macgyvette.livejournal.com/'><b>macgyvette</b></a></span> to come so she can share in the fun.  I also would mind sharing a room with her.  However we're not there yet so there are still three possible outcomes by that time, still together, good friends and not talking.  I think the first two would still work for this possibility, but the third wouldn't.<br /><br />It's fun to day dream about the future.
</description>
<comments>http://legostud.livejournal.com/6085.html</comments>
<lj:security>public</lj:security>
</item>
-
	<item>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://legostud.livejournal.com/5882.html</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2006 04:41:29 GMT</pubDate>
<title>Wow what a day</title>
<link>http://legostud.livejournal.com/5882.html</link>
-
	<description>
Went to Manchester to today with <span class='ljuser' lj:user='macgyvette' style='white-space: nowrap;'><a href='http://macgyvette.livejournal.com/profile'><img src='http://stat.livejournal.com/img/userinfo.gif' alt='[info]' width='17' height='17' style='vertical-align: bottom; border: 0;' /></a><a href='http://macgyvette.livejournal.com/'><b>macgyvette</b></a></span> to work on the Lego Millyard and I had so much fun that I'm still a little over whelmed.  I'm even having trouble organizing my thoughts enough to write this.  Imagine being on the best date ever and then mixing it with your favorite hobby.<br /><br />Today started out a little bumpy, because [insert boston accent] she got like wicked lost.  I started thinking that she might have forgotten to come or something had happened to her.  I was planning on calling her house around noon just to check. <br /><br />Once I found her, everything worked out.  I really can't believe how comfortable I am around her.  I know that there is this line of what is appropriate to say and at what times, but I'm completely clueless.  She accepted this.<br /><br />I heard so many great stories about her family and friends today.  I can't wait to actually meet someone of them.  She made one remark about how her siblings have all gotten married to people who have great parents.  I know I have great parents so this is a good sign for me.  Hopefully reading this doesn't scare her, I'm just looking down the road.<br /><br />I'm looking forward to seeing her again.  Might be during our NELUG meeting on Tuesday or Saturday at the Science Museum.  I should still have tickets.  Will need to check tomorrow.<br /><br />Maybe I can see her another time this week.  Her Mom's not feeling good so she might be busy.  I hope she gets better soon.  <br /><br />I have more, but I'm going to waiting until tomorrow since I need sleep.
</description>
<comments>http://legostud.livejournal.com/5882.html</comments>
<lj:security>public</lj:security>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>


